[
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "He ___ play tennis very well.",
      "optionA": "can",
      "optionB": "must",
      "optionC": "should",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "___ you like another drink?",
      "optionA": "Could",
      "optionB": "Should",
      "optionC": "Would",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "If you travel. You ___ take your camera.",
      "optionA": "must",
      "optionB": "should",
      "optionC": "ought to",
      "rightOption": "b"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "You ___ pass the exam if you don't study.",
      "optionA": "won't",
      "optionB": "wouldn't",
      "optionC": "mustn't",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "You ___ talk loudly in the library.",
      "optionA": "couldn't",
      "optionB": "mustn't",
      "optionC": "wouldn't",
      "rightOption": "b"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "___ I borrow your pen.",
      "optionA": "Must",
      "optionB": "Will",
      "optionC": "Shall",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "Excuse me. ___ I answer the phone",
      "optionA": "Will",
      "optionB": "Would",
      "optionC": "May",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "You ___ be over 21 to buy liquor.",
      "optionA": "must",
      "optionB": "may",
      "optionC": "should",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "It's late. This child ___ be in bed",
      "optionA": "ought to",
      "optionB": "could",
      "optionC": "will",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "It's late. My parents ___ be sleeping.",
      "optionA": "shall",
      "optionB": "might",
      "optionC": "would",
      "rightOption": "b"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "I wish I ___ run faster.",
      "optionA": "could",
      "optionB": "would",
      "optionC": "ought to",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "This time tomorrow we ___ be traveling.",
      "optionA": "will",
      "optionB": "can't",
      "optionC": "might",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "Waiter! ___ I have the menu please?",
      "optionA": "Must",
      "optionB": "Should",
      "optionC": "Could",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "You ___ drive so fast here.",
      "optionA": "couldn't",
      "optionB": "wouldn't",
      "optionC": "shouldn't",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "Children ___ drink alcohol.",
      "optionA": "mustn't",
      "optionB": "wouldn't",
      "optionC": "won't",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "I ___ go out tonight. I have to study.",
      "optionA": "won't",
      "optionB": "wouldn't",
      "optionC": "couldn't",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "Children ___ drink alcohol.",
      "optionA": "mustn't",
      "optionB": "wouldn't",
      "optionC": "won't",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "Spain ___ be very hot in the summer.",
      "optionA": "could",
      "optionB": "can",
      "optionC": "should",
      "rightOption": "b"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "Everybody ___ eat less junk food",
      "optionA": "should",
      "optionB": "can",
      "optionC": "might",
      "rightOption": "a"
    }
  },
  {
    "question":
    {
      "prompt": "You have a cold. You ___ stay home.",
      "optionA": "may",
      "optionB": "could",
      "optionC": "should",
      "rightOption": "c"
    }
  }
]
